<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog
                      http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-5.0.xsd"
>

    <changeSet id="seed-company-1" author="minhdat">
        <preConditions onFail="MARK_RAN">
            <sqlCheck expectedResult="0">
                SELECT COUNT(*) FROM companies;
            </sqlCheck>
        </preConditions>

        <insert tableName="accounts">
            <column name="account_id" valueNumeric="2"/>
            <column name="username" value="mbbank"/>
            <column name="email" value="mbbank@gmail.com"/>
            <column name="password" value="$2a$10$cNkKjLeLzT/fqEBYRNc3yuUbEc3rH6ZVH9hIIqzDnR3mbIBs4tuDO"/>
            <column name="enabled" valueBoolean="true"/>
        </insert>

        <sql><![CDATA[
            INSERT INTO companies (
                account_id,
                name,
                description,
                logo,
                cover_photo,
                website,
                phone,
                size,
                verified
            )
            VALUES (
                       2,
                       'MB Bank',
                       'Ngân hàng TMCP Quân Đội (MB)
                        Về chúng tôi
                        Với tầm nhìn "Trở thành Doanh nghiệp số, Tập đoàn tài chính dẫn đầu" cùng mục tiêu "Top 3 thị trường về hiệu quả, hướng đến Top đầu châu Á”, MB đã và đang tiếp tục xây dựng, phát triển trong và ngoài nước, nhằm đáp ứng yêu cầu chuyển dịch số, mục tiêu tăng trưởng kinh doanh và nâng cao năng lực cạnh tranh.
                        Sở hữu đội ngũ hơn 10.000 nhân sự, trong đó có hơn 1.000 MBITers – chiếm 10% tổng nhân sự toàn Ngân hàng – nằm trong top đầu các ngân hàng tại Việt Nam về tỷ lệ nhân sự thuộc nhóm Công nghệ và Đổi mới. MB đang không ngừng đầu tư mạnh mẽ cho hệ thống, con người và kinh doanh nền tảng nhằm đem đến những trải nghiệm xuất sắc nhất cho khách hàng, đồng thời xây dựng môi trường làm việc hạnh phúc, bền vững cho người MB.
                        Tự hào là Ngân hàng Số số 01 Việt Nam, phục vụ hơn 30 triệu khách hàng cá nhân và doanh nghiệp trên toàn quốc.
                        Việt Nam hiện có 07 ứng dụng đạt trên 10 triệu người dùng (theo số liệu của Bộ Thông tin và Truyền thông năm 2023), và MB là ngân hàng duy nhất góp mặt trong danh sách đầy tự hào này. Tính đến hết năm 2024, MB chính thức chinh phục cột mốc 30 triệu khách hàng – tương đương 30% dân số Việt Nam – và đã cùng người dùng thực hiện 6,5 tỷ giao dịch trên kênh số, giữ vững vị trí Top 1 về quy mô giao dịch NAPAS (Công ty Cổ phần Thanh toán Quốc gia Việt Nam).
                        Riêng ứng dụng App MBBank ghi nhận tần suất cao điểm lên tới 20 triệu giao dịch mỗi ngày, vận hành trên nền tảng hệ thống ổn định, an toàn và bảo mật cao.
                        Môi trường làm việc bền vững, hạnh phúc
                        Năm 2024 đánh dấu cột mốc MB30 về văn hóa và con người với hai giải thưởng uy tín: “Sustainable Workplace Awards – Doanh nghiệp có môi trường làm việc bền vững” do HR Asia Awards trao tặng và “Happiness At Work – Doanh nghiệp có Nguồn nhân lực Hạnh phúc” do Anphabe vinh danh.
                        Đặc biệt, MB chính thức được xướng tên trong hạng mục “Vietnam Best IT Companies 2025” do cộng đồng ứng viên ITviec bình chọn. Chúng tôi tiếp tục tìm kiếm những nhân tố xuất sắc, sáng tạo và đam mê công nghệ, đồng thời cam kết mang đến những giá trị và trải nghiệm tốt nhất cho mỗi cá nhân khi gia nhập tổ chức.',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/v1766052143/MB_bank_logo_b9twwz.jpg',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/v1766052143/MB_bank_logo_b9twwz.jpg',
                       'https://careers.mbbank.com.vn/home-page',
                       '0987654321',
                       'ENTERPRISE',
                       TRUE
                   )
            ]]></sql>

    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="seed-company-2" author="minhdat">
        <insert tableName="accounts">
            <column name="account_id" valueNumeric="3"/>
            <column name="username" value="tymex"/>
            <column name="email" value="tymex@gmail.com"/>
            <column name="password" value="$2a$10$cNkKjLeLzT/fqEBYRNc3yuUbEc3rH6ZVH9hIIqzDnR3mbIBs4tuDO"/>
            <column name="enabled" valueBoolean="true"/>
        </insert>

        <sql><![CDATA[
            INSERT INTO companies (
                account_id,
                name,
                description,
                logo,
                cover_photo,
                website,
                phone,
                size,
                verified
            )
            VALUES (
                       3,
                       'TymeX',
                       'TymeX is a part of Tyme Group - one of the world’s fastest-growing digital banking groups.
                        Tyme Group is one of the world’s fastest-growing digital banking groups, building high-tech and high-touch banks in fast-growing, emerging markets. Headquartered in Singapore with a Technology and product Development Hub in Vietnam, Tyme designs, builds, and commercializes digital banks for emerging markets, with particular expertise in serving under-served and under-banked populations.
                        Established in 2016, TymeX has been Tyme Group''s Product & Technology Development Hub, bringing together engineering and product people who share a global mission to become serial bank builders, shaping the future of banking through technology. We build products with the principle of finding the right balance between the digital and physical worlds.
                        We have proudly provided the banking platform as a service for:
                        TymeBank, based in South Africa, is one of the world’s fastest-growing digital banks, with over 7 million customers since launching in February 2019.
                        GoTyme Bank, based in the Philippines, is a joint venture between the Gokongwei Group and Tyme Group with the official launch in October 2022 and onboarded more than 1 million customers in less than nine months.',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/v1766233662/Screenshot_2025-12-20_192650_nkwii4.png',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/v1766233662/Screenshot_2025-12-20_192650_nkwii4.png',
                       'https://vietnam.tyme.com/',
                       '0987654321',
                       'ENTERPRISE',
                       TRUE
                   )
            ]]></sql>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="seed-company-3" author="minhdat">
        <insert tableName="accounts">
            <column name="account_id" valueNumeric="4"/>
            <column name="username" value="nab"/>
            <column name="email" value="nab@gmail.com"/>
            <column name="password" value="$2a$10$cNkKjLeLzT/fqEBYRNc3yuUbEc3rH6ZVH9hIIqzDnR3mbIBs4tuDO"/>
            <column name="enabled" valueBoolean="true"/>
        </insert>

        <sql><![CDATA[
            INSERT INTO companies (
                account_id,
                name,
                description,
                logo,
                cover_photo,
                website,
                phone,
                size,
                verified
            )
            VALUES (
                       4,
                       'NAB Innovation Centre Vietnam',
                       'The NAB Innovation Centre Vietnam is owned by NAB - Australia’s largest business bank.
                        The NAB Innovation Centre Vietnam (NAB Vietnam) is part of National Australia Bank (NAB) Technology & Enterprise Operations division. The mission of the NAB Vietnam is to connect the talents of Vietnam to NAB and together improve the lives of those in the Vietnam technology community.
                        As Australia’s largest business bank, NAB is focused on delivering great experiences for customers. To do this it uses modern technologies, alongside great technology talent including leading software engineers, cloud experts and quality engineers.
                        We’re working on interesting projects to help NAB’s 10 million customers: By joining us, local software engineers will have access to a wide variety of projects and opportunities, working closely with colleagues in Australia and with global partners such as AWS and Microsoft to take advantage of the latest modern technologies.
                        We’re investing in you: We strive to create not only a great place to work, but also the best technology centre for tech engineers to thrive.
                        It’s more than just a career!
                        We believe in people with ideas and dreams, and we want you to achieve your aspirations. If you have an appetite to learn, grow and elevate others around you, this is the place for you!',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/Screenshot_2025-12-20_193330_y4lxps.png',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/Screenshot_2025-12-20_193330_y4lxps.png',
                       'https://nab.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/nab_careers',
                       '0987654321',
                       'ENTERPRISE',
                       TRUE
                   )
            ]]></sql>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="seed-company-4" author="minhdat">
        <insert tableName="accounts">
            <column name="account_id" valueNumeric="5"/>
            <column name="username" value="viettel"/>
            <column name="email" value="viettel@gmail.com"/>
            <column name="password" value="$2a$10$cNkKjLeLzT/fqEBYRNc3yuUbEc3rH6ZVH9hIIqzDnR3mbIBs4tuDO"/>
            <column name="enabled" valueBoolean="true"/>
        </insert>

        <sql><![CDATA[
            INSERT INTO companies (
                account_id,
                name,
                description,
                logo,
                cover_photo,
                website,
                phone,
                size,
                verified
            )
            VALUES (
                       5,
                       'Viettel Group',
                       'SHOW US YOUR WAY
                        Tập đoàn Công nghiệp – Viễn thông Quân đội Viettel - Nơi làm việc tốt nhất Việt Nam 2017, 2018 ngành Viễn thông (theo khảo sát Anphabe) là Doanh nghiệp viễn thông có tốc độ tăng trưởng nhanh nhất thế giới, luôn đi đầu trong đổi mới sáng tạo và luôn lắng nghe, thấu hiểu để đem tới những dịch vụ tốt nhất cho khách hàng.
                        Viettel hiện là tập đoàn Viễn thông - CNTT lớn nhất Việt Nam, top 30 công ty viễn thông toàn cầu với hơn 13.000 nhân viên và đang kinh doanh tại 11 thị trường trải dài từ Châu Á, Châu Mỹ, Châu Phi. Bên cạnh viễn thông, Viettel còn tham gia vào lĩnh vực nghiên cứu sản xuất công nghệ cao, phát triển ứng dụng công nghệ số, hàng không vũ trụ và nhiều lĩnh vực khác.
                        Chúng tôi học hỏi lẫn nhau.
                        Chúng tôi tin tưởng nhân viên của mình ở những nhiệm vụ đầy thách thức.
                        Chúng tôi không chỉ là Viettel, chúng tôi là Việt Nam.',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/Screenshot_2025-12-20_193725_xc2kro.png',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/Screenshot_2025-12-20_193725_xc2kro.png',
                       'https://tuyendung.viettel.vn/',
                       '0987654321',
                       'ENTERPRISE',
                       TRUE
                   )
            ]]></sql>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="seed-company-5" author="minhdat">
        <insert tableName="accounts">
            <column name="account_id" valueNumeric="6"/>
            <column name="username" value="capgemini"/>
            <column name="email" value="capgemini@gmail.com"/>
            <column name="password" value="$2a$10$cNkKjLeLzT/fqEBYRNc3yuUbEc3rH6ZVH9hIIqzDnR3mbIBs4tuDO"/>
            <column name="enabled" valueBoolean="true"/>
        </insert>

        <sql><![CDATA[
            INSERT INTO companies (
                account_id,
                name,
                description,
                logo,
                cover_photo,
                website,
                phone,
                size,
                verified
            )
            VALUES (
                       6,
                       'Capgemini Vietnam',
                       'One of the world leading company in IT services
                        Overview about Capgemini Vietnam
                        Capgemini is a multicultural company of 300,000 people in nearly 50 countries, who work with world-renowned clients to find solutions to their most demanding challenges. As a global leader in consulting, digital transformation, technology and engineering services – with unrivaled sectorial expertise – we enable our clients to design and build tomorrow’s businesses, make the most of the opportunities offered by technology, and boost their competitiveness and agility.
                        Our Brand promise
                        | GET THE FUTURE YOU WANT
                        Our brand promise captures the spirit of our people, committed to bringing to life our purpose of unleashing human energy through technology for a sustainable and inclusive future. We want our teams, our clients, our partners, and our communities to feel that change can happen the way they want it to, and that we will help them achieve it.
                        Reimagining the way we work
                        Hybrid working is becoming a day-to-day reality at Capgemini. Underpinned by our trust-based managerial culture, we aim to empower everyone, in all countries, to deliver exceptional work, contributing to an inclusive and sustainable future for our people, our clients, and society.',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/Screenshot_2025-12-20_194211_xyctij.png',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/Screenshot_2025-12-20_194211_xyctij.png',
                       'https://www.capgemini.com/',
                       '0987654321',
                       'ENTERPRISE',
                       TRUE
                   )
            ]]></sql>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="seed-company-6" author="minhdat">
        <insert tableName="accounts">
            <column name="account_id" valueNumeric="7"/>
            <column name="username" value="bosch"/>
            <column name="email" value="bosch@gmail.com"/>
            <column name="password" value="$2a$10$cNkKjLeLzT/fqEBYRNc3yuUbEc3rH6ZVH9hIIqzDnR3mbIBs4tuDO"/>
            <column name="enabled" valueBoolean="true"/>
        </insert>

        <sql><![CDATA[
            INSERT INTO companies (
                account_id,
                name,
                description,
                logo,
                cover_photo,
                website,
                phone,
                size,
                verified
            )
            VALUES (
                       7,
                       'Bosch Global Software Technologies Company Limited',
                       'The Bosch Group is a leading global supplier of technology and services
                        The Bosch Group is a leading global supplier of technology and services. Its operations have been divided into four business sectors: Automotive Technology, Industrial Technology, Consumer Goods, and Energy and Building Technology.
                        The Bosch Group comprises Robert Bosch GmbH and its roughly 460 subsidiaries and regional companies in some 60 countries. If its sales and service partners are included, then Bosch is represented in roughly 150 countries.
                        Bosch Global Software Technologies Company Limited (BGSV) is 100% owned subsidiary of Robert Bosch GmbH - one of the world’s leading global suppliers of technology and services, offering end-to-end Engineering, IT, and Business Solutions.
                        Starting its operation from 2010 at Etown 2 in HCMC, BGSV is the first software development center of Bosch in Southeast Asia. BGSV nowadays have over 4,000 associates, with a global footprint and presence in the US, Europe, and the Asia Pacific region.
                        With our unique ability to offer end-to-end solutions that connect sensors, software, and services, we enable businesses to move from the traditional to digital or improve businesses by introducing a digital element in their products and processes.',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/Screenshot_2025-12-20_194513_gsfrhh.png',
                       'https://res.cloudinary.com/dfwttyfwk/image/upload/Screenshot_2025-12-20_194513_gsfrhh.png',
                       'https://www.bosch.com.vn/',
                       '0987654321',
                       'ENTERPRISE',
                       TRUE
                   )
            ]]></sql>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="update-column-companies-2" author="minhdat">
        <update tableName="companies">
            <column name="country" value="Việt Nam"/>
            <column name="industry" value="Ngân hàng"/>
            <column name="overtime_policy" value="Không có"/>
            <column name="working_days" value="Thứ 2 - Thứ 6"/>
            <where>account_id = 2</where>
        </update>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="update-column-companies-4" author="minhdat">
        <update tableName="companies">
            <column name="country" value="Singapore"/>
            <column name="industry" value="Ngân hàng"/>
            <column name="overtime_policy" value="Không có"/>
            <column name="working_days" value="Thứ 2 - Thứ 6"/>
            <where>account_id = 3</where>
        </update>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="update-column-companies-5" author="minhdat">
        <update tableName="companies">
            <column name="country" value="Australia"/>
            <column name="industry" value="Ngân hàng"/>
            <column name="overtime_policy" value="Không có"/>
            <column name="working_days" value="Thứ 2 - Thứ 6"/>
            <where>account_id = 4</where>
        </update>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="update-column-companies-6" author="minhdat">
        <update tableName="companies">
            <column name="country" value="Việt Nam"/>
            <column name="industry" value="Viễn thông"/>
            <column name="overtime_policy" value="Không có"/>
            <column name="working_days" value="Thứ 2 - Thứ 6"/>
            <where>account_id = 5</where>
        </update>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="update-column-companies-7" author="minhdat">
        <update tableName="companies">
            <column name="country" value="France"/>
            <column name="industry" value="Dịch vụ và tư vấn IT"/>
            <column name="overtime_policy" value="Không có"/>
            <column name="working_days" value="Thứ 2 - Thứ 6"/>
            <where>account_id = 6</where>
        </update>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="update-column-companies-8" author="minhdat">
        <update tableName="companies">
            <column name="country" value="Germany"/>
            <column name="industry" value="Dịch vụ và tư vấn IT"/>
            <column name="overtime_policy" value="Không có"/>
            <column name="working_days" value="Thứ 2 - Thứ 6"/>
            <where>account_id = 7</where>
        </update>
    </changeSet>


</databaseChangeLog>